<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Kings And Queens Game</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_game">NewGameActivity</string>
    <string name="page_1"> \n     They say that as humans, we often don’t cherish our relationships with others until they are gone. Rather it be an unruly teen who has a bad relationship with his mother, or a married couple who often get into disputes; its only when they are gone from the world do people truly think about the good times they had with them, when they only thought about the bad times when they were still with us. To put it in more relatable terms, a school friendship. You’ve been friends with many people in your school years, but as you grow up, you slowly leave them behind; and often, you think about what it would be like if you were still friends with them, not leaving them behind to pursue your own future, your own goals. What if you could reunite with your old friends from school, would you do it? I never thought about such things before I was thrust into a situation where that reunion with old friends happened. This is a story about how I, Justin, came to the harsh realization that we are fragile, and we must always remember what we had in the past and what we have in the present, before it’s painfully taken away from you. \n \n
It was nine P.M., a long day of classes finally over, and I’m walking back to my dormitory to get some well-deserved rest. Earlier, I had stopped by the convenience store to pick up some snacks to prepare for my study session; sugar and caffeine being a college students’ best friend, I could not forget to get the essentials, chocolate, soda, and coffee. It’s normally desolate at this time of night, but it felt even more so this time, more… ominous. My dorm is quite a way from my class, about a fifteen-minute walk give or take, and just as I was nearing the walkway that leads to my dorm, I hear a rustle in the distance. Normally I would pay this no mind; I always hear such noises when walking back to my dorm in the middle of the night, it was probably just some squirrel or leaves falling. On the other hand, something was different about this rustle; it was constant, never leaving my range of hearing. I assume it was just my nerves getting to me, so I pop open my bag of MM’s to get my mind off the distraction in the distance. However, just as I popped a few in my mouth, I hear a loud stomp about ten feet behind me. Combined with the constant rustling and the stomp I just heard, I decided to turn around, not out of curiosity, but out of fear. \n \n       As you would expect of a typical horror movie, when I turned around, nobody was there. Thinking I’m going crazy and that was just my own stomp which I confused for another, I turned back around… and was greeted by a sharp pain in the side of my neck. Was it a bug bite, did I run into a hanging branch? Before I could confirm what it was that stuck me, my vision started to blur, my ears began to ring extremely loudly, and my legs started to feel like jelly. For something to be this fast acting, this could not be an ordinary bite or poisonous sting. As I began to succumb to whatever toxic substance had dug its claws into me, I brought up whatever strength I had left in me to find the source of the attack. I turned my head to my right, and I saw a figure. Being that my vision was pretty much gone, all I could make out was a shadow, and distorted mumbling coming from the figure’s direction. My breathing and pulse slowing down at a rapid pace, not able to feel my limbs anymore, and my vision completely blank, I fall to the pavement. Is this it? Is my life over in a flash? Not being able to finish my senior year of college, right at the clasp of victory? These thoughts go by in a instant, and the last thing I hear is the loud thunk of the shaken-up soda can exploding on the ground.
</string>
    <string name="page_2">  \n     When I awoke, it feels like the first time I drunk in college and had a massive hangover, except times a hundred. It took a solid two minutes for my eyes to adjust to the lighting in the room; or lack thereof. Being that I could feel my limbs again I took a large stretch to get the blood flowing back into my extremities.  When my eyes started to function normally again, I take a wide look around the room, and I see a bunch of other people who are passed out, people who are already up and socializing with others, and a select few just beginning to wake up like myself. My senses mostly coming back to me, I finally realize that I’m sitting on a desk that’s chained up to the floor via ball and chain, and I’m tied to the ball and chain from my foot, like a prisoner. My ears make a giant pop and I suddenly hear chatter, although not normal chatter, but nervous mumblings, throughout the…. Facility? I’m not exactly sure where this is, but it resembles a giant warehouse, except there was no storage, it was just a couple dozen of desks with occupants in each of them. I could not see too far out into the distance, as the lights are very dim, but by the sound of chatter far out in the distance, I can tell that this place is large. \n \n      Out of instinct of being a typical student, I reach into my pocket to grab my phone to check the time, but there was nothing; all of our belongings are seemingly confiscated. Am I imprisoned? Did I do something wrong? Why is this happening? These questions rushed to my head in an instant once I realized the situation I was truly in. I look around in my immediate vicinity to see three other desks, also holding their own person. They are all face down, seemingly still under the spell of whatever the hell it was that knocked us out to being with. In doing this, I notice that desks are spread out in groups of four; is this some sort of sick game? No game can be fun if you’re forced into it, right? Before I reach out to try and wake up the person sitting adjacent to me, a loud siren blared throughout the warehouse. There were four sirens, I’m assuming one on each corner of the building, each blasting a blinding red light and extremely loud… music? It was something distorted, and nothing I’ve ever heard of, but it was loud enough to wake up everyone who was not already awake in the facility. \n \n The dim lighting that glowed in the facility shut off for a second, and was then replaced by ceiling lights bright enough to light up a baseball stadium. Immediately, I am shocked by what I see; what I originally thought was just a couple dozen desks turned out to be a far underestimate, quickly counting by groups of fours, there were well over eighty desks scattered throughout the warehouse. One thing that took me by a surprise is that the groups of four are separated by gender, there is not a single group with mixed genders. This also ties into my idea of this being a game, is this some sort of weird boy’s vs. girl’s contest? Why would they painfully force us into this, though, some sort of punishment? The previous mumblings were now loud conversations heard throughout the building, and the first thing I noticed was multiple different language. I noticed Mandarin, Hindi, Japanese, and Russian to name a few. This brought another question to mind, how would they kidnap people across the globe, if that was the case? The next course of action I took was to look around at my group, three other guys with startled expressions on their faces greet me back. The scary part was not the look on their faces, no, it was that I recognized all three of them. My old friends from junior high and high school, Quin, Forrest, and Colston.</string>
    <string name="page_3">  \n     “Woah, woah, you guys?!” I say, in surprise. It had been quite a while since I’ve seen them, and I had assumed we had all went our separate ways after school, but now, this happens? What exactly is going on? \n \n
“J-Justin?!” Quin blurts out, getting the first word out of the group. “We haven’t seen each other in a long time, and I should be happy, but the situation we’re in… am I dreaming?” \n \n
What he’s saying is correct, this would normally be a happy reunion between two best friends, but after being forcibly kidnapped, this couldn’t be a happy meeting, not in the least. We need to find out what’s going on before that can happen. Quin and I were best friends my senior year of high school, we were both massive geeks, and we shared the same interests in Anime and Manga, which was rare to find another fan of in my sports centric school.  We related very well due to that common interest, and even talked for a bit after we graduated, but as time went on, we moved on and stopped communicating, as school friends often do… until now, that is. \n \n
“I’m sorry to say, but this seems very much real” Colston says while he’s pinching his arm. I haven’t seen Colston since junior high years since we went to different high schools, but we still communicated over Facebook. Colston was the stereotypical cool popular guy but was also accepting to the geeky types such as myself, which is why our friendship worked well; I was the brains and he was the cool. \n \n
“Colston? We haven’t seen each other in years, why would it suddenly happen after we were abducted?” I say, with a concerning look on my face. \n \n
“I think it’s a joke, maybe it’s just a pran- “. \n \n
“No, this has something to do with Justin” Forrest, the last one of the three to speak, interrupts Colston before he could finish his sentence. “We all know Justin, but Colston, Quin, and I don’t know each other, so that means we were brought here because we have a connection to Justin, right?”  \n \n
Forrest and I were lunch buddies in High School, but we knew each other all the way back in junior high. We were (I still am, I’m not sure about Forrest) both introverted and didn’t talk to a lot of people, so naturally it would be hard to find a spot in the cafeteria to sit and eat without things getting awkward, so we gave each other company. If there is one thing I certainly don’t miss about public school, it’s lunch period. Not only were we lunch buddies, but he also acted as my tutor in the various classes we both shared. I consider myself rather intelligent, but Forrest was on another level, acing every exam with ease with little studying while I ended up sweating bullets on them, calculus and chemistry being my main foes. With his level of intellect, it was only natural he’d come to this conclusion; the conclusion that this weird situation has to do with me.
 </string>
    <string name="page_4">  \n     “Forrest, I know just as little as you all do” I say, trying to ease some of the recent tension built. “We should talk things through before jumping into any major conclusions. I was shot by some sort of poison and woke up here. I assume you three also had the same fate?”  \n \n
“I know you too well, Justin, and I know you would never arrange something like this, but it definitely has to do with you, and whoever is the mastermind behind this whole thing picked us because we have a relationship to you”. After making his case, Forrest starts to scan the room, and notices there’s another group of four next to his desk, an all-girl group. He waves to get their attention. \n \n
“Yes?” A girl who looked around our age with long black hair responds. “Are you guys also friends?” \n \n
“Yes and no, I’m only friends with this guy.” Forrest says as he points at me. “Do you happen to know him too? I’m trying to get to the bottom of this.” \n \n
She takes a five second glance at me, looks away, and then takes another short glance, and replies “I’m afraid I don’t. The only people I know here are the other three in my group.” \n \n
Forrest makes a slight smirk and responds facing me “So my theory was half right. It seems like every group of four has a central piece, and the three other members are revolved around that piece, but they don’t necessarily know each other, only the center piece. Sort of like a king.” \n \n
“Yeah, but that also means I’m not the sole reason as to why everyone was kidnapped, but whoever created this event chose a “king” or “queen” and chose three other members that these “center pieces” knew, for what reason, we do not know. Also, you should have noticed everyone wouldn’t be connected to me, the people here do not all seem to be from America, and I certainly never traveled abroad and met this many people.” \n \n
“Can we keep all of this technical talk out of the conversation? It doesn’t have to be that complicated, and the first thing we should be talking about is how the hell do we get out of here, we’re chained down like prisoners for fuck’s sake!” Colston replies bluntly. He was always one to use coarse language, but usually to accomplish his jokes, not out of anger, or in this case, fear and uncertainty. I’ve never seen Colston like this before but put any cool person in a situation like this, and they are bound to change. \n \n
“This totally reminds me of a Manga I read once, named Battle Royale” Quin finally speaks up, and of course he brings up his favorite topic. “Students suddenly kidnapped out of the blue and forced to participate in a killing game! Even though, not all of us are students, and we aren’t all in the same age range…” He says as he scans around the immediate area. \n \n
He was right, there were groups with people in the teens, their early twenties, and, I’m assuming, thirty plus. Naturally, their groups consisted of people around their age as well, since they are all friends with the king or queen. \n \n
“You know, Quin, I know you love Manga and Anime to death, but this is real, and it’s not something to sound excited about!” I reply, upset at his enthusiasm about the situation we’re in. \n \n
Before Quin could reply, the girl Forrest previously spoke to waved frantically to get our attention. “Psst, look! I think that’s the man behind this silly reunion. But… what is he wearing?” She says while pointing north.
</string>
    <string name ="page_5"> \n     “I don’t know what the hell you’re talking about! Does it look like I would be capable of this? You of all people should know that would not be the case! You might think just because you’re a know it all that you have this figured out, but you need to think again.” \n \n
“No need for the outburst, I was simply hypothesizing one of the many reasons as to why we’re all here, and I decided to share it with you. What happened to the shy person I’ve known throughout school?" After making his case, Forrest starts to scan the room, and notices there’s another group of four next to his desk, an all-girl group. He waves to get their attention. \n \n
“Yes?” A girl who looked around our age with long black hair responds. “Are you guys also friends?” \n \n
“Yes and no, I’m only friends with this guy.” Forrest says as he points at me. “Do you happen to know him too? I’m trying to get to the bottom of this.” \n \n
She takes a five second glance at me, looks away, and then takes another short glance, and replies “I’m afraid I don’t. The only people I know here are the other three in my group.” \n \n
Forrest makes a smirk and responds facing me “So my theory that you almost chewed my head off for was half right. It seems like every group of four has a central piece, and the three other members are revolved around that piece, but they don’t necessarily know each other, only the center piece. Sort of like a king.” \n \n
“Yeah, but that also means I’m not the sole reason as to why everyone was kidnapped, but whoever created this event chose a “king” or “queen” and chose three other members that these “center pieces” knew, for what reason, we do not know. Also, you should have noticed everyone wouldn’t be connected to me, the people here do not all seem to be from America, and I certainly never traveled abroad and met this many people. Also, no, before you ask, I did not volunteer to become this so called king.” \n \n
“Can we keep all of this technical talk out of the conversation? It doesn’t have to be that complicated, and the first thing we should be talking about is how the hell do we get out of here, we’re chained down like prisoners for fuck’s sake!” Colston replies bluntly. He was always one to use coarse language, but usually to accomplish his jokes, not out of anger, or in this case, fear and uncertainty. I’ve never seen Colston like this before but put any cool person in a situation like this, and they are bound to change. \n \n
“This totally reminds me of a Manga I read once, named Battle Royale” Quin finally speaks up, and of course he brings up his favorite topic. “Students suddenly kidnapped out of the blue and forced to participate in a killing game! Even though, not all of us are students, and we aren’t all in the same age range…” He says as he scans around the immediate area. \n \n
He was right, there were groups with people in the teens, their early twenties, and, I’m assuming, thirty plus. Naturally, their groups consisted of people around their age as well, since they are all friends with the king or queen. \n \n
“You know, Quin, I know you love Manga and Anime to death, but this is real, and it’s not something to sound excited about!” I reply, upset at his enthusiasm about the situation we’re in. \n \n
Before Quin could reply, the girl Forrest previously spoke to waved frantically to get our attention. “Psst, look! I think that’s the man behind this silly reunion. But… what is he wearing?” She says while pointing north.
</string>
    <string name ="page_6">\n      Indeed, a man and a woman enter the room, the man wearing a solid black suit and tie, while the woman dons a solid black jacket and a hat that says ‘Assistant’. What was odd about what the man was wearing that the girl noticed was that he had his face covered with a mask, a simple half black half white opera mask that covered the top half of his face, maybe to hide his identity?  Why would the assistant not have their identity hidden as well? Is this man extremely important? He reaches into his pocket and pulls out some sort of handheld device that contained a single button. He presses it, and a giant projector screen slowly scrolls down, wide enough to cover the entire front of the facility. In doing this, all the groups become deathly silent, all gazes now turned to the presentation in front. The man takes center stage while the assistant is to the left of him. He pulls out a microphone, seemingly about to start some sort of speech. \n \n
“Good morning, ladies and gentlemen, kings and queens!” The audio feedback is extremely loud, I guess the four sirens on each side of the room also double as amplifiers. “And welcome to the Kings and Queens game, an exciting experience that will surely change all of your lives!” \n \n
The mumblings throughout the facility suddenly come back, surely discussion what this “Kings and Queens” game is, and why we were brought here and restrained in such a… non-game like manner? The man’s voice is very jolly, and it’s not deep and menacing, but, well, the best way I can describe it would be a lower pitched Mickey Mouse. \n \n
“I know you’re all concerned and confused, and rightfully so, but I assure you, I will explain everything in due time, so long as you keep silent.” His cheerful tone sounded a little more ominous at the end of his sentence. His assistant also has a handheld device in her hand, and a slide show presentation is booted up onto the projector screen behind the man. It looks like she will oversee the slideshow. He continues “As you may have already noticed, you are set up into groups of four, separated by gender, and consisting of friends of the king or queen. The purpose of this presentation is to explain the rules of the game, not to answer questions such as how were the kings and queens chosen, what’s the point of this game, and why were we kidnapped? These questions will either be answered overtime by the game directors, or you must find out these answers yourselves over the course of the game.” The assistant hands the man a strange bottle of liquid and he takes a few gulps, giving the presentation a momentary pause. \n \n
I glanced around the room, while it was still dead silent, the looks on people’s faces spoke louder than any words could; it was pure bewilderment and fear. Fear of the uncertainty of what’s to come, of the rules of this ‘game’. Glancing at my own team, Quin and Colston both look like they could have a heart attack at any second, likely for completely different reasons. Quin likes the unknown, and always wanted to go on an adventure, all the fiction reading really got his imagination burning constantly so he is likely excited about this situation which reminds him so much of his fiction stories. Forrest on the other hand looks calm, as if he’s coming up in advance what the rules could possibly be, and what sort of ‘game’ this really is.
</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game"></string>
    <string name="title_activity_stats">Stats</string>
</resources>
