<resources>
    <string name="app_name">The Kings And Queens Game</string>
    <string name="title_activity_new_game">NewGameActivity</string>
    <string name="page_1"> \n     They say that as humans, we often don’t cherish our relationships with others until they are gone. Rather it be an unruly teen who has a bad relationship with his mother, or a married couple who often get into disputes; its only when they are gone from the world do people truly think about the good times they had with them, when they only thought about the bad times when they were still with us. To put it in more relatable terms, a school friendship. You’ve been friends with many people in your school years, but as you grow up, you slowly leave them behind; and often, you think about what it would be like if you were still friends with them, not leaving them behind to pursue your own future, your own goals. What if you could reunite with your old friends from school, would you do it? I never thought about such things before I was thrust into a situation where that reunion with old friends happened. This is a story about how I came to the harsh realization that we are fragile, and we must always remember what we had in the past and what we have in the present, before it’s painfully taken away from you.
It was nine P.M., a long day of classes finally over, and I’m walking back to my dormitory to get some well-deserved rest. Earlier, I had stopped by the convenience store to pick up some snacks to prepare for my study session; sugar and caffeine being a college students’ best friend, I could not forget to get the essentials, chocolate, soda, and coffee. It’s normally desolate at this time of night, but it felt even more so this time, more… ominous. My dorm is quite a way from my class, about a fifteen-minute walk give or take, and just as I was nearing the walkway that leads to my dorm, I hear a rustle in the distance. Normally I would pay this no mind; I always hear such noises when walking back to my dorm in the middle of the night, it was probably just some squirrel or leaves falling. On the other hand, something was different about this rustle; it was constant, never leaving my range of hearing. I assume it was just my nerves getting to me, so I pop open my bag of MM’s to get my mind off the distraction in the distance. However, just as I popped a few in my mouth, I hear a loud stomp about ten feet behind me. Combined with the constant rustling and the stomp I just heard, I decided to turn around, not out of curiosity, but out of fear. \n \n       As you would expect of a typical horror movie, when I turned around, nobody was there. Thinking I’m going crazy and that was just my own stomp which I confused for another, I turned back around… and was greeted by a sharp pain in the side of my neck. Was it a bug bite, did I run into a hanging branch? Before I could confirm what it was that stuck me, my vision started to blur, my ears began to ring extremely loudly, and my legs started to feel like jelly. For something to be this fast acting, this could not be an ordinary bite or poisonous sting. As I began to succumb to whatever toxic substance had dug its claws into me, I brought up whatever strength I had left in me to find the source of the attack. I turned my head to my right, and I saw a figure. Being that my vision was pretty much gone, all I could make out was a shadow, and distorted mumbling coming from the figure’s direction. My breathing and pulse slowing down at a rapid pace, not able to feel my limbs anymore, and my vision completely blank, I fall to the pavement. Is this it? Is my life over in a flash? Not being able to finish my senior year of college, right at the clasp of victory? These thoughts go by in a instant, and the last thing I hear is the loud thunk of the shaken-up soda can exploding on the ground.
</string>
    <string name="page_2">  \n     When I awoke, it feels like the first time I drunk in college and had a massive hangover, except times a hundred. It took a solid two minutes for my eyes to adjust to the lighting in the room; or lack thereof. Being that I could feel my limbs again I took a large stretch to get the blood flowing back into my extremities.  When my eyes started to function normally again, I take a wide look around the room, and I see a bunch of other people who are passed out, people who are already up and socializing with others, and a select few just beginning to wake up like myself. My senses mostly coming back to me, I finally realize that I’m sitting on a desk that’s chained up to the floor via ball and chain, and I’m tied to the ball and chain from my foot, like a prisoner. My ears make a giant pop and I suddenly hear chatter, although not normal chatter, but nervous mumblings, throughout the…. Facility? I’m not exactly sure where this is, but it resembles a giant warehouse, except there was no storage, it was just a couple dozen of desks with occupants in each of them. I could not see too far out into the distance, as the lights are very dim, but by the sound of chatter far out in the distance, I can tell that this place is large. Out of instinct of being a typical student, I reach into my pocket to grab my phone to check the time, but there was nothing; all of our belongings are seemingly confiscated. Am I imprisoned? Did I do something wrong? Why is this happening? These questions rushed to my head in an instant once I realized the situation I was truly in. I look around in my immediate vicinity to see three other desks, also holding their own person. They are all face down, seemingly still under the spell of whatever the hell it was that knocked us out to being with. In doing this, I notice that desks are spread out in groups of four; is this some sort of sick game? No game can be fun if you’re forced into it, right? Before I reach out to try and wake up the person sitting adjacent to me, a loud siren blared throughout the warehouse. There were four sirens, I’m assuming one on each corner of the building, each blasting a blinding light and extremely loud… music? It was something distorted, and nothing I’ve ever heard of, but it was loud enough to wake up everyone who was not already awake in the facility. The dim lighting shut off for a second and replaced by ceiling lights bright enough to light up a football stadium. Immediately, I am shocked by what I see; what I originally thought was just a couple dozen desks turned out to be a far underestimate, quickly counting by groups of fours, there were well over eighty desks scattered throughout the warehouse. One thing that took me by a surprise is that the groups of four are separated by gender, there is not a single group with mixed genders. This also ties into my idea of this being a game, is this some sort of weird boy’s vs. girl’s contest? Why would they painfully force us into this, though, some sort of punishment? The previous mumblings were now loud conversations heard throughout the building, and the first thing I noticed was multiple different language. I noticed Mandarin, Hindi, Japanese, and Russian to name a few. This brought another question to mind, how would they kidnap people across the globe, if that was the case? The next course of action I took was to look around at my group, three other guys with startled expressions on their faces greet me back. The scary part was not the look on their faces, no, it was that I recognized all three of them. My old friends from junior high and high school, Quin, Forrest, and Colston.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game"></string>
</resources>
